Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Production files, Circa 1970-1992; MS2040 Series 4
  - Production Files, Tape Cover for Gargoyle # 28, #29, #34, and Tina Fulker's Tender Hooks, 1986-1987 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Resolution Production Co. Correspondence and related material, 1987 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, AAPEX Duplication materials for Tape #36, undated (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Correspondence, Permission to record author's work, 1986-1989 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, I'm In Love With The Morton Salt Girl page mechanicals, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, I'm In Love With The Morton Salt Girl book cover and related material, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Echt & Ersatz material, nd, undated (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, A Brief Look at Three of Washington, D.C. 's Most Important Literary Magazines page mechanicals, nd, undated (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Blank Like Me page covers, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Blank Like Me rough copy, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Jukebox photos and examples for cover, Circa 1980 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Jukebox page mechanicals, Circa 1980 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Jukebox manuscript, Circa 1980 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Jukebox sample copies, Circa 1980 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, Jukebox author correspondence, Circa 1980 (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, D.C. Magazines cover page mechanical, nd, undated (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, D.C. Magazines interview transcripts, nd, undated (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, D.C. Magazines Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, D.C. Magazines Release Forms, 1979-1981 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, D.C. Magazines Ads for book, nd, undated (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Mavericks Cover proof, 1982-1983 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Mavericks Correspondence, background info. for book, 1979-1982 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Mavericks page mechanicals, 1982-1983 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Mavericks Bluelines, 1982-1983 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Mavericks notes, 1982-1983 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, The Love Letter Hack book covers, Circa 1982 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, The Love Letter Hack page mechanicals, Circa 1982 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, The Love Letter Hack edited copy, Circa 1982 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Natural History page mechanicals, Circa 1985 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Natural History page mechanicals, Circa 1985 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Natural History notes, Circa 1985 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, The Love Letter Hack Bluelines, Circa 1982 (Box 184, Folder 7)
- Administrative files, 1978-1990; MS2040 Series 5
  This series consists of one box of various documents used in the administration of Paycock Press from 1978 to 1990. Receipts and inventories from 1981, 1986 to 1987 and 1989 were used for tax purposes. A cumulative index of the writers and artists in Gargoyle, as well as award applications, grant proposal documents and copyright information were referred to by Peabody to solicit financial and literary support for the journal.
  - Miscellaneous, Gargoyle ink stamps (2), nd, undated (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Gargoyle ink stamps (2), nd, undated (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, Tax Receipts, 1981 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, Tax Receipts, 1986 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Tax Items, 1987 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Itemized Deductions, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, Cumulative Index of Issues, #1 26, nd, undated (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, G.E. Awards Applications, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines Applications, 1978-1989 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, NEA Grant Correspondence and Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Copyright and Library of Congress Applications and Correspondence, 1978-1989 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, Copyright and Library of Congress Applications and Instruction Manual, 1978-1990 (Box 185, Folder 10)
- Flyers and brochures, 1996-2009; Series 6; 0.25 Linear Feet 1 slim letter size document box
  Arranged chronologically by year.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains flyers and brochures related to the literary community in Washington, D.C. There are flyers for new publications from local publishing houses such as Word Works, reading series such as Kensington Row, and events at local bookstores and writing workshops such as Chapters and the Writer's Center. The material dates from 1996-2009. These files were collected by Richard Peabody.
  - 1996-1999, Series 6 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - 2000-2002, Series 6 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - 2003-2009, Series 6 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Undated, Series 6 (Box 186, Folder 4)